# Bryan Shay

Willowick, OH 44095 ♦ (440) 840-2260 ♦ forgetfulmind@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> ◆ <u>gitHub</u> ◆ <u>Coding Portfolio</u>

## **Professional Summary**

Innovative and proactive Marketing Coordinator Studying Full-Stack Web Development desiring to bring knowledge and abilities developed over years of experience into pursuing challenging roles dedicated to increasing the visibility and understandability of products and applications.

Talented in content creation and coordination, project management, inventory management, and video prod with an exceptional attention to detail and excellent communication abilities.

## **Technical Skills**

#### **Languages Studied:**

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- jQuery
- Node.js

#### **Coding Projects:**

- Moodtoob Developed by a team of four, built with Javascript and CSS stylings, utilizing Face++
  Face Detection API and Youtube Data V3 API to take a selfie from the user, read their emotional
  state from the image, and make a set of music video recommendations to match their mood
  - o <u>www.moodtoob.com</u>
  - o <u>GitHub Repository</u>
- Weather Forecast Dashboard Built with Javascript and CSS stylings, utilizing OpenWeatherAPI, this application allows a user to search for cities and see a one and five day forecast.
  - o <u>Deployed on GitHub Pages</u>
  - o <u>GitHub Repository</u>
- Dynamic Day Planner Built with Javascript and CSS stylings, utilizing Day.js, this application allows a user to create a simple day planner and know the time of day.
  - o <u>Deployed on GitHub Pages</u>
  - o <u>GitHub Repository</u>

## **Skills**

- Marketing Collateral Management
- Media relations
- Database management
- Campaign management
- Reporting and documentation
- Proofreading
- Fact Checking
- Project Management

- Time management
- Interdepartmental collaboration
- Tradeshows and events
- Communications Management
- Email blasts and newsletters
- Video Development/Production
- Inventory Management
- Organization

## **Work History**

## Marketing Coordinator, 05/2018 to Current

The Telos Alliance - Cleveland, OH

- Website CMS Administration
- Contact Management Administration
- Forum Administration
- Internal/External Email Campaigns
  - o Research/Development/Execution
- Content Creation/Coordination
- Inventory Management/Maintenance
- Trade Show Preparation Physical Assembly/Gear Coordination
- Internal/External Video Communication
  - o Development/Production/Editing
- Interviews/Content Creation Coordination for External Publication
- Photography Product/Staff/Other
- Video Streaming
- Domestic/International Shipping Coordination

#### Marketing Assistant, 02/2015 to 05/2018

The Telos Alliance - Cleveland, OH

- Website Content Population
- Contact Management Assistance
- Email Campaign Assistance
- Content Creation Assistance
- Inventory Management Assistance
- Trade Show Preparation Assistance

• External Video Communication - Development/Production/Editing

## CAD Librarian / Documentation Control Assistant, 06/2011 to 02/2015

#### The Telos Alliance - Cleveland, OH

- PCB Component Footprint and Symbol Library Creation/Management
- PCB Component Footprint and Symbol Creation
- PCB Component Data Sheet Library Creation/Management
- PCB CAD Tool Troubleshooting/Assistance
- Research and Development Documentation Control Assistance

## **General Manager,** 05/2009 to 06/2011

## Georgio's Oven Fresh Pizza - Willoughby, OH

- Staff Management
- Inventory Management/Ordering
- Store Maintenance
- Schedule Creation/Management
- Food Preparation/Execution
- Customer Service

## **Education**

- Case Western Reserve University Full Stack Flex Coding Bootcamp
  - Currently Enrolled
- Lakeland Community College Willoughby, OH
  - Completed credits towards Associate of Science Degree
- University of South Carolina Columbia Columbia, SC
  - Completed credits towards Marine Science Degree
- High School Diploma: 2007
  - o Notre Dame Cathedral Latin High School Chardon, OH